Register of the Atlantic Council of the United States Records, 1950-1986
Hoover Institution Archives
- SUBJECT FILE, 1950-1985
  - Bills
    - 1972
      - May (Folder 3)
      - June (Folder 4)
      - July (Folder 5)
      - August (Folder 6)
      - September (83, Folder 1)
      - October (Folder 2)
      - November (Folder 3)
      - December (Folder 4)
      - various months (Folder 5)
    - 1973
      - January (Folder 6)
      - February (Folder 7)
      - March (84, Folder 1)
      - April (Folder 2)
      - May (Folder 3)
      - June (Folder 4)
      - July (Folder 5)
      - August (Folder 6)
      - September-October (85, Folder 1)
      - November-December (Folder 2)
    - 1974
      - January (Folder 3)
      - February-March (Folder 4)
      - April-May (Folder 5)
      - June (86, Folder 1)
      - July-August (Folder 2)
      - September-October (Folder 3)
      - November (Folder 4)
      - December (87, Folder 1)
    - Accounting and legal, 1968 (Folder 2)
    - B and P Promotions, 1967-68 (Folder 3)
    - Batt, Bates and Company
      - 1962 (Folder 4)
      - 1962-63 (Folder 5)
    - Board meetings, 1968 (Folder 6)
    - Capital City Press, 1968 (Folder 7)
    - Chas. G. Stott & Co., 1968 (Folder 8)
    - College and University Program, 1968 (Folder 9)
    - CoMarco Data Services, Inc.
      - 1968 (Folder 10)
      - 1970-71 (Folder 11)
    - Copenhaver, 1962 (Folder 12)
    - Exspeedite Service, Inc., 1962 (Folder 13)
    - Gallant Incorporated
      - 1961-63 (Folder 14)
      - 1964 (Folder 15)
    - George Antone & Co.
      - 1962 (Folder 16)
      - 1963 (Folder 17)
    - Ginn's
      - 1961-62 (Folder 18)
      - 1963-64 (Folder 19)
      - 1968 (88, Folder 1)
    - Gist & Chairs, Inc.
      - 1962 (Folder 3)
      - 1963 (Folder 4)
      - 1964 (Folder 5)
      - 1968 (Folder 6)
    - Group Hospitalization, Inc.
      - 1963-64 (Folder 7)
      - 1964 (Folder 8)
    - Kelly Girl Service, Inc.
      - 1962 (Folder 9)
      - 1964 (Folder 10)
    - Literature and educational publications
      - 1963 (Folder 11)
      - 1968 (Folder 12)
    - Maintenance and repair, 1963 (Folder 13)
    - Meetings and receptions
      - 1963 (Folder 14)
      - 1964 (Folder 15)
    - Monumental Printing Company
      - 1963 (Folder 16)
      - 1969 (Folder 17)
      - 1971 (Folder 18)
    - Office supplies and expenses, 1968 (Folder 19)
    - Pitney-Bowes, Inc.
      - 1962 (Folder 20)
      - 1963 (Folder 21)
      - 1964 (Folder 22)
      - 1968 (Folder 23)
    - Printing and mimeographing, 1968 (Folder 24)
    - Promotion, public relations, representation, 1968 (Folder 25)
    - Robotyping Corporation
      - 1962 (Folder 26)
      - 1963 (Folder 27)
    - Robotyping Letter Service, 1968 (Folder 28)
    - Service contracts, 1962-66 (Folder 29)
    - Smith-Corona Marchant, Inc., 1964 (Folder 30)
    - Stott & Co., Inc.
      - 1962 (Folder 31)
      - 1963 (Folder 32)
    - Telephone, 1968 (89, Folder 1-2)
    - Underwood Corporation, 1963 (Folder 3)
    - United Publishing Co., Inc.
      - 1962 (Folder 4)
      - 1963 (Folder 5)
      - 1968 (Folder 6)
    - W. D. Campbell Company, 1962 (Folder 7)
    - Western Union, 1968 (Folder 8)
    - Xerox, 1968 (Folder 9)
  - Biographies (Folder 10)
  - Bloomfield, Lincoln, "The Future of the UN: A Strategy for Like-Minded Nations,", August 1976 (Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors
    - 1972 (Folder 12)
    - 1973 (Folder 13)
    - 1974 (Folder 14)
    - Acceptance of Board membership, 1961-62 (90, Folder 1)
    - Biographies (Folder 2)
    - Meetings
      - 1962 March 9 (Folder 4)
      - 1970
        - January 13 (Folder 5)
        - June 10 (Folder 6)
      - 1971
        - January 20 (Folder 7)
        - April 14 (Folder 8)
        - September 8 (91, Folder 1-2)
      - 1972
        - June 7 (Folder 3)
        - October 11 (Folder 4)
      - 1973
        - January 11 (Folder 5)
        - June 14 (Folder 6)
        - October 25 (Folder 7)
      - 1974
        - January 24 (Folder 8-9)
        - April 10 (Folder 10)
        - June 19 (Folder 11)
        - October 16 (92, Folder 1)
      - Expenses, 1963 (Folder 2)
    - Memoranda to
      - 1963 (Folder 3-4)
      - 1964
        - January-May (Folder 5)
        - June-December (Folder 6)
      - 1966 (Folder 7)
      - 1967 (Folder 8)
      - 1968 (93, Folder 1)
      - 1969 (Folder 2)
      - 1970 (Folder 3)
      - 1971 (Folder 4)
      - 1973 (Folder 5)
      - 1974 (Folder 6)
      - 1975 (Folder 7)
      - 1975-78 (Folder 8)
    - Minutes of meetings
      - 1962 (Folder 9)
      - 1963 (Folder 10)
      - 1964 (94, Folder 1)
      - 1965 (Folder 2)
      - 1966 (Folder 3)
      - 1967 (Folder 4)
      - 1968 (Folder 5)
      - 1969 (Folder 6)
      - 1970
        - January 13 (Folder 7)
        - June 10 (Folder 8)
      - 1971
        - January 20 (Folder 9)
        - April 14 (Folder 10)
        - June 10 (Folder 11)
        - September 8 (Folder 12)
      - 1973
        - April 19 (Folder 13)
        - June 14 (Folder 14)
        - October 25 (95, Folder 1)
      - 1974
        - January 24 (Folder 2)
        - April 10 (Folder 3)
        - June 19 (Folder 4)
        - October 16 (Folder 5)
      - 1975-78 (Folder 6)
    - New directors, 1972 (Folder 7)
    - President's letter, March 20, 1984 (Folder 8)
    - Refusal of Board membership (Folder 9)
  - Book exhibits, 1969 (Folder 10)
  - Book orders, 1972-73 (Folder 11)
  - Book Project (Folder 12)
  - Boone, W. F., "NATO - Keystone of Defense," reprint, U.S. Naval Institute Proceedings, April 1959 (Folder 13)
  - Botelho, Viscount Do, "Economic Exploitation of the Atlantic Ocean,", October 1969 (Folder 14)
  - Bradley, Gene E.
    - General (Folder 15)
    - Book (Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1967-68 (Folder 17)
    - Report on Atlantic Institute Technology Meeting, November 16, 1967 (Folder 18)
    - "Trans-Atlantic Corporate Task Force on Development Planning for the " 1967, 1970s (Folder 19)
  - Bradley/Cerf trip, July 1967 (96, Folder 1-2)
  - Breeder Reactor, 1977 (Folder 3)
  - Brewster, Daniel B. (Folder 4)
  - Brimmer, Andrew (Folder 5)
  - Brimmer, Andrew and Henry S. Terrell, "The Economic Potential of Black Capitalism,", December 29, 1969 (Folder 6)
  - British American Associates (Folder 7)
  - British Atlantic Committee, 1971-74 (Folder 8)
  - Brochure
    - 1969-1970 (Folder 9-10)
    - 1971 (Folder 11)
  - Brookings Institution
    - General (Folder 12)
    - Roundtable on Atlantic Community for Corporation Pre- dents and Board Chairmen (Folder 13)
    - Study on the relationship between foreign investment and trade, 1968-69 (97, Folder 1)
  - Brosio, Manlio (Folder 2)
  - Brown University, Class of reunion, 1912 (Folder 3)
  - Brundage, Percival F.
    - 1971-73 (Folder 4)
    - General (Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1971-77 (Folder 6)
  - Brussels meeting, June 2, 1963 (Folder 7)
  - Buchan, Alastair, "The Evolution of NATO,", November 1961 (Folder 8)
  - Budget
    - 1963 (Folder 9)
    - 1964 (Folder 10)
    - 1965 (Folder 11)
    - 1966 (Folder 12)
    - 1968 (Folder 13)
    - 1969 (Folder 14)
  - Building the American-European Market - Planning for the 1970s
    - General (Folder 15)
    - Bursk review (Folder 16)
    - Luncheon (Folder 17)
    - Preface (Folder 18)
    - Synopsis (Folder 19)
    - Table of contents (Folder 20)
  - Burden, William A. M., "Improved Methods of Concerting Foreign Policies and Strategies Within the Western Alliance,", December 1961 (Folder 21)
  - Burgess, W. Randolph
    - General (98, Folder 1)
    - Address before the Graduate School of Banking, June 13, 1958 (Folder 2)
    - Articles (Folder 3)
    - Athens Assembly of the ATA, September 1961 (Folder 4)
    - Atlantic Community Quarterly article, April 1964 (Folder 5)
    - Canada speeches (Folder 6)
    - "Cherishing Public Credit," speech, George Washington Dinner, American Good Government society, April 27, 1963 (Folder 8)
    - Correspondence
      - 1970 October-December (Folder 9)
      - 1972-73 (Folder 10)
      - 1974 (Folder 11)
      - Brown University, 1964-66 (Folder 12)
      - John Foster Dulles Oral History Project, 1968 (Folder 13)
    - Dacor House speech, January 6, 1964 (Folder 14)
    - De Gaulle article (Folder 15)
    - "The Economic Consequences of General De Gaulle," (Folder 16)
      - article, Political Science Quarterly, No. 4
      - December 1963
    - "Economic Education and the National Welfare," article, NASSP Bulletin, November 1975 (99, Folder 1)
    - "Education and International Understanding,", September 1968 (Folder 2)
    - "Education for International Business Responsibility," speech, National Foreign Trade Council, November 18, 1963 (Folder 3)
    - "Education for International Understanding," article, December 1968 (Folder 4)
    - Federal Reserve Bank of New York Monthly Review, article, November 1964 (Folder 5)
    - "Future of the Atlantic Community," speech, DePauw University, April 10, 1964 (Folder 6)
    - "Future of the Atlantic Community," speech, Georgetown University, November 17, 1965 (Folder 7)
    - "How to Assure Continuity of Progress," speech, Texas A & M, September 16-17, 1965 (Folder 8)
    - "International Implications of Fifty Years of the Federal Reserve System," article, April 1965 (Folder 9)
    - "Keys to Continuing Prosperity," address, Babson Institute, October 27, 1965 (Folder 10)
    - Knox College (Folder 11)
    - Latin American trip, 1968 (Folder 12)
    - Lisbon meeting, June 1962 (Folder 13)
    - Maine State Safety Conference, August 28-29, 1963 (Folder 14)
    - Malta (Folder 15)
    - Management Problems of International Organizations as Illustrated in the OPEC and OECD," (Folder 16)
    - "Men and Institutions," speech, Stonier School of Banking, June 12, 1964 (Folder 17)
    - NATO speeches (100, Folder 1)
    - "The New Administration and the International Economy," speech, November 1968 (Folder 2)
    - Open market article, November 1964 (Folder 3)
    - "The Personal Factor in Atlantic Community Leadership," address, Georgetown University Forum, August 21, 1966 (Folder 4)
    - Remarks, Copenhagen, September 25, 1962 (Folder 5)
    - Speeches (Folder 6-7)
    - "Teaching Atlantic Cooperation," speech, National Council for the Social Studies, November 26, 1964 (Folder 8)
    - "Toward an Atlantic Central Bank,", February 4, 1975 (Folder 9)
    - Trips, 1969
      - June (Europe) (Folder 10)
      - July (England and Brussels) (Folder 11)
    - "U.S. Policy in the Atlantic Community," speech, Private Planning Association of Canada, November 1966 (Folder 12)
    - Washington Post article, April 27, 1966 (Folder 13)
    - "The West Learns to Work Together," speech, Pitts- burgh, February 1963 (Folder 14)
    - World cruise, February-April 1965 (Folder 15)
  - Burgess book promotion (Folder 16)
  - Burgess reception, April 9, 1969 (Folder 17)
  - Bush for President, 1980 (Folder 18)
  - Business and Industry Advisory Committee (B.I.A.C.) (Folder 19)
  - Business Council for Internation Understanding (BCIU) (Folder 20)
  - By-laws (Folder 21)
  - Cabinet Committee meetings, 1967
    - April 19 (101, Folder 1)
    - October 25 (Folder 2)
  - Cables
    - 1969 (Folder 3)
    - 1970 (Folder 4)
  - CAEC, 1970 (Folder 5)
  - Callaghan, Thomas A., U.S./European Economic Cooperation in Military and Civil Technology, September 1975 (Folder 6)
  - Canada
    - Energy sources (Folder 7)
    - Nuclear energy (Folder 8)
    - Oil and petroleum (Folder 9)
  - Canadian-American Committee, 1975 (102, Folder 1)
  - Canadian-American trade relations, 1963-66 (Folder 2)
  - Canadian study (proposed), 1978 (Folder 3)
  - Canadian Trade Committee Conference, Ottawa, November 14-18, 1966 (Folder 4)
  - Canadian-US relations (Folder 5)
  - Canadian Working Group, 1980-81 (Folder 6)
  - Cancer research conference, 1970 (Folder 7)
  - Capital City Press (Folder 8-11)
  - Capital markets, 1967 (Folder 12)
  - Capital markets, 1967 (103, Folder 1)
  - Carmoy, Guy de (Folder 2)
  - Carr, Patrick (Folder 3)
  - Carr, William
    - "The 'Face' of Mao Tse-Tung,", 1968 (Folder 4)
    - "Military Assistance - Cargo or Concepts,", October 1967 (Folder 5)
  - Carstens, Karl, "A Turning Point in German Policy: The Moscow Treaty,", August 1970 (Folder 6)
  - Catlin, George (Folder 7)
  - Center for Strategic Studies, Georgetown University, 1966-67 (Folder 8)
  - Center for Strategic and International Studies, Georgetown University, 1978 (Folder 9)
  - Center for War/Peace Studies (Folder 10)
  - Centre d'Information et de Documentation Atlantique, 1963-64 (Folder 11)
  - Centre International de Formation Europeenne, 1961-63 (Folder 12)
  - Century Association, 1969-1974 (Folder 13)
  - Cercle de l'Opinion, 1963-64 (Folder 14)
  - Cerf, Jay H., "European Investment Climate, 1967," speech, November 1, 1967 (Folder 15)
  - Certificate of Incorporation (104, Folder 1)
  - CETI (Folder 2)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the U.S. (Folder 3)
  - Charles G. Stott, 1968-69 (Folder 4)
  - China (Folder 5-8)
  - China Project, 1980 (Folder 9)
  - Christmas mailings
    - 1965 (Folder 10)
    - 1966 (Folder 11)
  - Chronology of events, September 7, 1960 to January 20, 1962 (105, Folder 1)
  - Cincinnati Council on World Affairs
    - 1964-65 (Folder 2)
    - 1970 (Folder 3)
    - 1974 (Folder 4)
    - Seminar, October 1973 (Folder 5)
  - Claremont International Monetary Conference, March 7-10, 1969 (Folder 6)
  - Clayton, William L. (Folder 7-8)
  - Clayton Fund (Folder 9)
  - Cleveland, Harlan
    - General (Folder 10)
    - "The Irrelevance of Anti-Commitment,", 1968 (Folder 11)
    - Obligations of Power: American Diplomacy in the Search for Peace, review of in the Political Science Quarterly, 1966 (Folder 12)
  - Cleveland Council on World Affairs
    - 1964-65 (Folder 13)
    - 1966 Cleveland Tour of NATO Television Teams, October 12-14, 1966 (Folder 14)
  - Clippings
    - 1961
      - April-June (Folder 15)
      - August (Folder 16)
      - October-December (106, Folder 1)
    - 1962
      - January (Folder 2-4)
      - February-May (Folder 5)
      - June (Folder 6)
      - June (107, Folder 1)
      - July (Folder 2)
    - 1969 (Folder 3)
    - 1970 (Folder 4)
    - 1971 (Folder 5)
    - 1971-72 (Folder 6)
    - 1972 (Folder 7-8)
    - 1972-73 (Folder 9)
    - 1973 (Folder 10)
    - 1974 (108, Folder 1)
    - 1975-76 (Folder 2)
    - 1978-79 (Folder 3)
    - 1979 (Folder 4)
  - Clippings on ACUS books (Folder 5)
  - Clokie Proposal (Folder 6)
  - Club of Rome (Folder 7)
  - Coleman, John R., "Economic Understanding and Social Values," (Folder 8)
  - College and university program
    - 1964 (Folder 9)
    - 1969 (109, Folder 1)
  - College of Europe (Belgium) (Folder 2)
  - Columbia University Seminar, 1965 (Folder 3)
  - Co-Marco Data Service, 1968-69 (Folder 4)
  - Comissao Portuguesa do Atlantico, Bulletin, No., 31, October 1968 (Folder 5)
  - Commission on the Organization of the Government for the Conduct of Foreign Policy, Survey of Previous Reports on Organizational Reform in the Foreign Affairs Community, John Elting Treat, June 1974 (Folder 6-8)
  - Committee for Atlantic Economic Cooperation (CAEC)
    - 1967-69 (110, Folder 1)
    - 1967-1970 (Folder 2)
    - 1968 (Folder 3)
    - General (Folder 4-5)
    - ADELA European Project (Folder 6)
    - Atlantic Institute/Battelle (Folder 7)
    - Cabinet Committee (Folder 8)
    - Conference on Direct Investment in the Atlantic Area, May 1-4, 1969
      - General (Folder 9-11)
      - Conference working papers (111, Folder 1-2)
      - Invitees (Folder 4)
      - Participation (Folder 5)
      - Press release, January 2, 1969 (Folder 6)
      - Steering Committee meetings (Folder 7)
    - Conferences, European investment in the U.S., Spring 1969 (Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1967-68
      - 1967 (Folder 9)
      - 1967-68 (Folder 10)
      - Merchant, Livingston (Folder 11)
    - Draft terms of reference (Folder 12)
    - Economic Committee (Folder 13)
    - Follow-up Conference on European Direct Investment in the United States, December 1969 (Folder 14)
    - Meeting, Conference, September 1969, and 1970 (Folder 15)
    - Meetings
      - 1967 (Folder 16)
      - 1968
        - May 24-25 (Folder 17)
        - November 7-8 (Folder 18-19)
        - 1969 September 23 (Folder 20-21)
      - U.S. position meeting, n.d. (Folder 22)
    - Press release, November 17, 1967 (Folder 23)
    - Tuthill, John W., correspondence, 1969 (Folder 24)
  - Committee for a National Trade Policy (Folder 25)
  - Committee for a National Trade Policy (112, Folder 1-2)
  - Committee of Correspondence, 1970 (Folder 3)
  - Committee on Atlantic Studies, 1967 (Folder 4)
  - Committee on the Challenges of Modern Society (CCMS) (Folder 5-6)
  - Committee on NATO (Folder 7)
  - Committee on the Present Danger
    - 1976-77 (Folder 8)
    - 1979 (Folder 9)
    - 1980-81 (Folder 10)
  - Committee on Relations With the Administration and Congress (Folder 11)
  - Committee on Science and Technology, 1967 (Folder 12)
  - Committee on Trade, Monetary and Corporate Policy
    - 1965 (Folder 13)
    - 1965 (113, Folder 1-2)
    - 1965-67 (Folder 3)
    - 1968 (Folder 4)
    - 1969 (Folder 5)
    - Blumenthal, W. Michael, testimony to Senate Banking and Currency Committee, April 28, 1969 (Folder 6)
    - Business Abroad, July 1968 (Folder 7)
    - Committee for a National Trade Policy (Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1967-69 (Folder 9)
    - Greenwald, Joseph A., conversation with, May 29, 1967 (Folder 10)
    - Hight, John, report, 1968 (Folder 11)
    - May conference on investment, 1969 (Folder 12)
    - Meetings
      - 1967
        - March 14 (Folder 13)
        - May 19 (Folder 14)
      - 1968
        - January 8 (Folder 15)
        - June 5 (114, Folder 1)
      - (Non-Tariff Barriers), 1969 December 17 (Folder 2)
    - Members (Folder 3)
    - Peterson, Rudolph A., "Cooperation or Stagnation? A Time for Decision,", 1968 (Folder 4)
    - Polk, Judd, "United States' Economic Policy: A Comment on Directions and Mis-Directions,", March 1969 (Folder 5)
    - Proposed study on the relationship between investment and trade, 1968 (Folder 6)
    - "Strengthening the International Monetary System,", May 19, 1967 (Folder 7)
    - Umbrella Committee (Folder 8)
  - Comparative education (Folder 9)
  - Conant, Melvin A., "Political Aspects of a 'New World' Energy System,", May 1980 (Folder 10)
  - Conant Project, 1976 (Folder 11)
  - Conference Board, 1976 (Folder 12)
  - Conference for Corporation Executives, May 13-14, 1975 (Folder 13)
  - Conference on the Future of the Atlantic Alliance and Canada's Role in It, March 3-5, 1967 (Folder 14)
  - Conference on North Atlantic Community, May 31, 1957 (Folder 15)
  - Conferences
    - (Texas A & M University - SCONA), 1966 December (Folder 17)
    - 1969
      - General (Folder 18)
      - (University of Louisville), March 27 (Folder 19)
    - 1970 (Folder 20)
    - 1971 (115, Folder 1)
    - 1972 (Folder 2)
    - 1973 (Folder 3)
    - General (Folder 4)
    - "Atlantic Partnership and Economic Growth," Fontain- bleau, November 5-6, 1965 (Folder 5)
    - Battelle Memorial Institute Conferences on Environ- mental Quality (Folder 6)
    - Conference of the European Parliament with the Par- liaments of African States and Madagascar, Stras- bourg, June 19-24, 1961 (Folder 7)
    - Conference on the Atlantic Community
      - Georgetown University, 1965 November 12-17 (Folder 8)
      - 1967 (Folder 9)
      - 1969 March 14-19 (Folder 10)
      - 1971 (Folder 11)
      - 1975 (Folder 12)
    - Conference on Foreign Aspects of U.S. National Security, Washington, D.C., February 25, 1958 (Folder 13)
    - Conference on North Atlantic Community, Bruges, September 8-14, 1957 (Folder 14)
    - Conference on Secondary Education in Internatinal Affairs, Ditchley Park, October 17-19, 1967 (Folder 15)
    - Conference on Security and Cooperation in Europe and Negotiations on Mutual and Balanced Force Reductions (CSCE/MBFR), 1972-73 (Folder 16)
      - General (116, Folder 1-4)
      - Advisory Committee
        - Brzezinski, Zbigniew (Folder 5)
        - Burgess, W. Randolph (Folder 6)
        - Correspondence (Folder 7)
        - Meeting, October 10, 1972 (Folder 8)
        - Memoranda sent to members (117, Folder 1)
        - Study (Folder 2)
      - Correspondence
        - General (Folder 3)
        - Interdepartmental (Folder 4)
      - Press conferences and lists (Folder 5)
      - Requests for a copy of report (Folder 6)
      - Sattler, James (Folder 7)
      - Sattler pamphlet (Folder 8)
      - Study (Folder 9-19)
    - Conference on Strategies for Atlantic Technological Development, Rome, May 24-26, 1968 (118, Folder 1-2)
    - "The Corporate Stake in the Atlantic Alliance With Focus on Trade, Investment and Monetary Issues,", March 19-20, 1974 (Folder 3)
    - Deauville, May 25-28, 1967 (Folder 4)
    - Direct Investment in the Atlantic Area, Washington, D.C., May 1-4, 1969
      - General (Folder 5-8)
      - Ambassadors (Folder 9)
      - Clippings (119, Folder 1)
      - Committee for Atlantic Economic Cooperation (Folder 2)
      - Correspondence (Folder 3-4)
      - Countries represented
        - Belgium (Folder 5)
        - Canada (Folder 6)
        - Denmark (Folder 7)
        - France (Folder 8)
        - Germany (Folder 9)
        - Great Britain (Folder 10)
        - Greece (Folder 11)
        - Italy (Folder 12)
        - Japan (Folder 13)
        - Netherlands (120, Folder 1)
        - Norway (Folder 2)
        - Sweden (Folder 3)
        - Switzerland (Folder 4)
        - United States (Folder 5)
      - Dinners (Folder 6)
      - Expenses (Folder 7)
      - Hotel accommodations (Folder 8)
      - International organizations (Folder 9)
      - Katz, Stanley (Folder 10)
      - Media coverage (Folder 11)
      - Papers (Folder 12-13)
      - Participants, list of (Folder 14)
      - Peccei, Aurelio (Folder 15)
      - Post-conference materials (121, Folder 1)
      - Rolfe, Sidney E., "The International Corporation in Perspective" (Folder 2)
      - Summary of conference (Folder 3)
      - Translators (Folder 4)
      - Transportation (Folder 5)
    - Environmental quality, 1971 (Folder 6-7)
    - Europe-America Colloquium, Amsterdam, November 7-9, 1974 (Folder 8)
    - Europe-America Conference, Amsterdam, March 26-28, 1973
      - General (Folder 9-10)
      - Clippings (Folder 11)
      - Correspondence
        - 1972
          - May-July (Folder 12)
          - August-November (122, Folder 1)
        - 1972 December-1973 March (Folder 2)
      - Delegations, invitees, committees (Folder 3)
    - European Security Conference, March 19, 1970
      - General (Folder 4)
      - Ad Hoc Committee (Folder 5)
      - NATO Committee (Folder 6)
    - Fifth Atlantic Study Conference, September 7-12, 1964 (Folder 7)
    - Fontainebleau, November 5-6, 1965 (Folder 8)
    - Future Atlantic Alliance and Canada's Role, March 3-5, 1967 (Folder 9)
    - Goals and Strategy for Environmental Improvement in the Seventies, January 15-17, 1971
      - General (Folder 10)
      - Advance book orders (Folder 11)
      - Agenda (Folder 12)
      - Biographies of speakers (Folder 13)
      - Budgets (123, Folder 1)
      - Clippings (Folder 2)
      - Correspondence (Folder 3)
      - Embassy Row Hotel (Folder 4)
      - Final report (Folder 5)
      - Follow-up (Folder 6)
      - International invitees (Folder 7)
      - Invitations (Folder 8-9)
      - Managing the Environment (124, Folder 1-3)
      - Memoranda to participants (Folder 4)
      - Participants (Folder 5)
      - Press information (Folder 6)
      - Requests for papers (Folder 7)
      - Thank you letters (Folder 8)
      - Translators (Folder 9)
    - Inter-American Council of Young Political Leaders, proposal for the first conference of (Folder 10)